SARIT SOPITVETMONTREE

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Yokohama, Kanagawa 070-1262-9500 sarit.sopitvetmontree@gmail.com

PROFILE

Developer-turned-designer with strategy planning and design experience across AI agents, BtoB sales, and healthcare products. Trilingual (Thai/English/Japanese) with firm knowledge in frontend development, enabling effective collaboration with PMs and engineers to ship quality product.

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarit-sopitvetmontree/ **Portfolio** https://sarit-sopitvetmontree.github.io/Portfolio/

SKILL LANGUAGE

Design Strategy, Competitive research, User persona, User flow IA, Wireframing, UI design, Design system, Responsive design HTML, CSS, Typescript, React, Tailwind, VSCode, Git/Github

Japanese JLPT N2
English TOEIC 960 TOEFL 99
Thai Native

WORK EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

November 2024 - Present

Part-time: July 2024 - Present

Sales Marker - Al SaaS for BtoB business, Tokyo

- Lead the UX and UI design in a multi-designer team for an AI agent application
- Design sales workflow automation feature and run interface QA for a BtoB sales platform
- Maintain and evolve the design system and frontend codebase, ensuring consistency

Lead Product Designer

SIND - SaaS for Healthcare workers, Tokyo

- Define design strategy as the founding designer for an assistant app for hospital nurses
- Lead end-to-end design, from concept and IA to hi-fi design; achieve 93% user satisfaction
- Establish usage monitoring and analyze feedback to drive continuous improvement

UX Engineer Aug 2023 - October 2024

QunaSys - Quantum computer software development, Tokyo

- Build and iterate on web applications using Next.js, MUI, and related technologies
- Create and refine web application design based on user requests and feedback

Product Designer

Contract : July 2023 - October 2023

Digitech Fabrication - 3D printing service, Bangkok

- Define requirements, create a design system, and deliver hi-fi UI for a 3D printing service
- Collaborate with engineers to ship the website, contributing code as needed

EDUCATION & ACHIEVEMENT

The University of Tokyo 東京大学

April 2022 - March 2024

Master's Degree, Department of Aeronautics and Astronautics

Chulalongkorn University จุฬาลงกรณ์มหาวิทยาลัย

August 2017 - July 2021

Bachelor's Degree, Department of Mechanical Engineering

MEXT Scholarship Awarded the MEXT Scholarship by the Embassy of Japan in Thailand

2021

Olympiad in Informatics Selected to enter the 12th Thailand Olympiad of Informatics

2016

SARIT SOPITVETMONTREE

プロダクトデザイナー

神奈川県横浜市 070-1262-9500 sarit.sopitvetmontree@gmail.com

プロフィール

ソフトウェアエンジニアの経験を活かしたプロダクトデザイナーです。AIエージェント、BtoBセールス、ヘルスケアの領域で、戦略立案からUX/UIデザインまで一貫して担当してきました。フロントエンドの知見を活かし、PM・エンジニアと連携して開発と品質向上を推進します。日・英・タイの三言語での業務遂行が可能です。

Linkedin https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarit-sopitvetmontree/ **Portfolio** https://sarit-sopitvetmontree.github.io/Portfolio/

スキル言語

デザイン戦略、競合調査、ユーザーペルソナ、ユーザーフロー **日本語** JLPT N2 IA、ワイヤーフレーム、UIデザイン、デザインシステム、レスポンシブ **英語** TOEIC 960 TOEFL 99 HTML, CSS, Typescript, React, Tailwind, VSCode, Git/Github **タイ語** ネイティブ

職務経歴

プロダクトデザイナー 2024年11月 ~ 現在

Sales Marker - BtoB向けAI SaaS・東京

- AIエージェントアプリケーションのUX/UIデザインを、複数名のデザイナーチームでリード。
- BtoBセールスプラットフォームにおける営業ワークフロー自動化機能を設計。
- デザインシステムとフロントエンドのコードベースを維持・進化させ、全体整合と品質を確保。

リードデザイナー パートタイム:2024年7月 ~ 現在

SIND - 医療従事者向けSaaS・東京

- ファウンディングデザイナーとして、看護師向けアシスタントアプリのデザイン戦略を策定。
- コンセプト設計/IAからハイファイUIまで一貫して主導し、ユーザー満足度93%を達成。
- 利用状況のモニタリングとフィードバック分析の仕組みを構築し、継続的改善を推進。

UXエンジニア 2023年8月 ~ 2024年10月

業務委託: 2023年7月~2023年10月

2021

QunaSys - 量子コンピュータ向けソフトウェア開発・東京

- Next.js、MUI等を用いたWebアプリケーションを開発・改善。
- ユーザー要望とフィードバックに基づき、アプリケーションデザインを作成・洗練。

プロダクトデザイナー

Digitech Fabrication - 3Dプリンティングサービス・バンコク

- 要件定義、デザインシステムの構築、ハイファイUIの提供を担当。
- エンジニアと協業し、必要に応じてコードも実装してサイト公開に貢献。

学歴•受賞歴

東京大学 2022年4月 ~ 2024年3月

航空宇宙工学専攻 修士課程

チュラロンコン大学 2017年8月 ~ 2021年7月

機械工学科 学士

文部科学省 (MEXT) 奨学金 在タイ日本国大使館推薦

情報オリンピック 第12回タイ情報オリンピック選抜 2016